civilservice.gov.uk 2011-09-02

# Privacy policy

## Privacy policy

This page explains our privacy policy and how we will use and protect any information about you that you give us when you visit this website.

This privacy statement only covers Civil Service websites. It does not cover all sites that can be linked to from this site, so you should always be aware when you are moving to another site and read the privacy statement on that site.

## What information do we collect?

If you are a user with general public and anonymous access, the Civil Service website does not capture or store personal information about you but simply logs your IP address, which is automatically recognised by our web server. This is known as a ‘log file’ which we use to compile site usage statistics.

The site does not use cookies to collect user information.

We collect two kinds of information from visitors to this website: feedback; and email subscription details.

### Feedback

We welcome your feedback. If you contact us asking for information, we may need to contact other government departments to find that information. If your question is technical, we may need to pass it to our technology suppliers.

We do not pass on any of your personal information when dealing with your enquiry, unless you have given us permission to do so. Once we have replied to you, we keep a record of your message for audit purposes.

#### Email subscriptions

Some areas of this website offer email updates. To receive these email updates, you need to register, giving: your email address; a user name; and password. We do not share the information you provide with any third parties and we protect it in accordance with the Data Protection Act.

##### The Data Protection Act

Under the Data Protection Act, we have a legal duty to protect any information we collect from you. We use leading technologies and encryption software to safeguard your data, and keep strict security standards to prevent any unauthorised access to it.

We do not pass on your details to any third party or other government department.

Changes to this privacy policyIf this privacy policy changes in any way, we will place an updated version on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties.
